foreign
[Music]
please call the technician our mfds are
not working properly even though we had
replaced toner last week only
sure we'll call them right away
[Music]
I see the reason of your problem is
consumable
no we use genuine products only no sir
have you double checked as these are not
genuine Canon toners oh but these look
exactly like Originals how can one be
sure before buying that it's not a
genuine product very easy sir
buy from authorized dealers don't get
lured by the prices because in the long
run the damage is way more than the cost
you paid secondly check the Canon logo
and the Hallmark which is only available
with genuine donors and you must scan
the QR code on the CFS label and check
for its authenticity
fall quality output and low cost of
operations always use Canon genuine
products
Canon delighting you always